{
    "id": "aff08cba5b4e49cb8f046031a61a7ce6",
    "title": "Confusing Words Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I ………………. the papers to his office.",
            "description": "We use bring for movements to the place where the speaker or the listener is. We use take for movements to other places.",
            "answers": [
                "took",
                "brought",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "This is a lovely beach. Thanks for ………………… me here.",
            "description": "We use bring for movements to the place where the speaker or the listener is. We use take for movements to other places.",
            "answers": [
                "taking",
                "bringing",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "……………….. like swimming.",
            "description": "Before a noun with a determiner, both and both of are both possible.",
            "answers": [
                "Both my parents",
                "Both of my parents",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I …………….. my camera to James and I never saw it again.",
            "description": "To lend is to give. You lend something to somebody.",
            "answers": [
                "lent",
                "borrowed",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "What are the main differences ………………….. dogs, wolves and foxes?",
            "description": "We use between, not among, after difference.",
            "answers": [
                "between",
                "among",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I had ……………… unpleasant experience in the morning.",
            "description": "A little and a bit are not used with adjectives in attributive position.",
            "answers": [
                "a rather",
                "a bit",
                "a little"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The house ……………….. is very small.",
            "description": "That…in can mean where.",
            "answers": [
                "that I live in",
                "where I live",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "American football is very different ……………. soccer.",
            "description": "From and to are common in British English and than is common in American English.",
            "answers": [
                "from",
                "to",
                "than",
                "All of the above"
            ],
            "correct": 3
        },
        {
            "question": "At no time ……………… her self-control.",
            "description": "If a negative adverb comes at the beginning of a clause, it is usually followed by auxiliary verb + subject.",
            "answers": [
                "she did lose",
                "did she lose",
                "she lost"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I ………………. going to new places and meeting new people.",
            "description": "Very much does not come between like and its object.",
            "answers": [
                "like very much",
                "very much like",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "A crocodile starts life ………….. an egg.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "like",
                "as",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Could you ……………. if dad is in the garage?",
            "description": "Before ‘if’ we can use ‘see’ or ‘look to see’. Look is not used before if or whether. ",
            "answers": [
                "see",
                "look",
                "look to see"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        }
    ]
}